the whole of Gorlovka knows, but the bearded Budulai
вся Горловка знает а бородатый Будулай
doesn’t know, but somehow it’s not. It’s
не знает но это как-то не Это
true. I’m from the city of Khmelnitsk. Where are you
правда Я из города Хмельницке Вы откуда
from? I’m from the city of Gorlovka, I understand.
Я из города Горловки понял А какая
And what country is the city of Gorlovka?  there
А Вы как считаете Горловка это что
should be Russia or Ukraine, even
должна быть Россия или Украина даже
Russia Yeah, I understand that you are in favor of Russia
Россия Ага понял вы за то чтобы Россия
being like a city. Well, well, it deserves it.
типа была горв Да ну того заслуживает А
But look, I understand that you
вот смотрите Я так понимаю что вы в
lived in Gorlovka last damn year. Yes, yes,
чертом году жили в Горловке Да да
of course. I’m interested. I just lived in
конечно Вот мне интересно Я просто жил в
Khmelnitsky. I don’t quite know.  there True
Хмельницком Я не совсем знаю там Правда
or false You, it’s your
или неправда У вас же это же у вас
city council deputy who
депутата городского совета рыбака
stabbed a fisherman Yes, and in the river no no no
зарезали Да и в речку нет нет нет
well, a deputy of the Gorlovka city council
ну депутат горловского городского совета
A fisherman
Рыбак
stabbed at least VM the year of
зарезал по крайней мере ВМ году
this one who cut the shaft of the mayor of the city of
такого этого кто подил вал мэра города
Gorlovka in what year how how how his
Горловки в чем году как как как его
the name is now the mayor, let's
зовут сейчас уже вот мэра давайте
try right now,
попроб сейчас
this is not a fisherman at all, no, the fisherman was
так это совсем не рыбак нене рыбак был
not the mayor. The fisherman was
этим не мэром Рыбак был
a deputy, so Evgeniy Klep was your
депутатом так вот Евгений клеп был у вас
MR
МР
throat Yes, Klep Klep Klep Yes, that is,
горло Да клеп клеп клёп да то есть вот у
in 1914, in April, you had
вас в четырнадцатом году в апреле
some  people Yes, they came, what did they do to the
какие-то люди Да пришли что они сделали
elected mayor of Gorlovka? Well, these
с с избранным мэром Горловки Ну это
were some bandits there, well, I don’t know, I
какие-то бандиты были там ну я не знаю
don’t know, that’s what they did to the mayor of
не знаю вот что они сделали с мэром
Gorlovka in April of 1914, well,
Горловки в апреле четырнадцатого года ну
in the end, he’s alive and healthy, I don’t,
в конце концов он живой здоровый я не в
after all, what happened to  They did it to him, what
конце концов что с ним сделали что
happened? You lived in Gorlovka Yes, he
случилось Вот вы жили в Горловке Да он в
disappeared somewhere at one moment he
один момент пропал куда-то в один момент
disappeared Disappeared then then he
пропал Пропал вот потом потом он
appeared a month ago If it was in
появился меся ско месяце было Если в
April, well, this is a month, probably somewhere in
апреле ну это месяц наверно где-то в
June he was released,
июне его отпустили
that’s all the Internet
по это всё интернет
I remember I didn’t follow this much Well, yes,
помнит я мало следил за этим Ну
I disappeared. I went with him when we were
да пропал Я с ним ходил когда вот мы
talking. We had this team
общались У нас было этот коллектив
formed such that we decided to sweat for
сложился такой который решали на пот за
Ukraine or Russia, we came together with
Украиной или за Россией мы приходили с
him, he’s on two chairs on two
ним обща он на двух стульях на двух
chairs on two chairs, I understand to squirm
стульях на двух стульях поёрзать
Yes, some people don’t know him,
понимаю Да что его какие-то люди не знаю
I don’t know some people, he’s definitely not from
я не знаю какие-то люди это точно не с
our organization. Well, not from your
нашей организации Ну да не с вашей
organization. But some people. Yes, they
организации Но какие-то люди Да его
threw him in the basement because he didn’t
закинули на подвал потому что он не
want to. I don’t know. He was in the basement.  I wasn’t
хотел я не знаю Был он на подвале не был
in the basement, I know that he disappeared, then he
на подвале я знаю что он пропал потом он
appeared, a ransom was given for him, like,
появился выкуп за него ещё давали типа
well, it’s all been a long time ago, like a schedule, I
ну вот уже всё давно типа расписа я про
won’t tell you anything about it, you
это ничего не скажу вам
know what’s wrong, I know the history
ию сво голов знаете Капец Я знаю историю
of my Gorlovka, but I’m like that.
своей Горловки но я такого У нас у нас
in conversations with each other, don’t be so
даже в разговорах между собой тако не
good, but look, when he
ходи хорошо а вот смотри когда вот он
disappeared And who uh and who And maybe you know
пропал А кто э а кто А может быть знаете
such a mayor, this people’s mayor in Orloki,
такой мэр был этот народный мэр в орлоки
maybe about this what what what is a people’s
может про это что что что такое народный
mayor Well, the people who elected the mayor
мэр Ну вот народ который выбрал мэра
are not the people Here  just klyop was popular
нене народ Вот как раз клёп был народным
he was chosen by choice no oh Klyopa was before
его выбрали на выбо нет о Клёпа был до
that until what year Wait stop stop
того до чего года Подождите стоп стоп
Who who chose Yes who chose him in the
Кто кто выбрал Да кто выбрал его в
twelfth year Klyopa Yes well, this is everyday life it
двенадцатом году Клёпа Да ну это быт это
was an all-Ukrainian election Yes, the inhabitants of
было всеукраинские выборы Да жители
the city, that is, look I have wait
горос то есть смотрите Я имею подождите
wait  It’s not you who will interrupt me
подождите не вы меня перебивать будете
or my thought Tell me Just when there
или меня мысль Скажите Просто когда
were other elections, yes
другие выборы были да
Tell me there were elections when they elected the
Скажите были выборы когда выбрали
people’s people And how they elected it right on the
народного мра А как это выбирали пря на
Maidan How did you choose the president so you
Майдане Как вы выбрали президента так
chose I understand correctly that you were
выбрали я правильно понимаю что вы
just on the square in Gorlovka, how many of you
просто на площади в Горловке сколько вас
were there?  you chose some
было людей что вы выбрали себе какого-то
mayor for yourself, are you going to interrupt me now or
мэра вы мне сейчас будете перебивать или
I’ll tell you why? Tell me, don’t
я вам расскажу чем так Расскажите не
tell me how many people chose
Расскажите сколько людей выбрало у вас
this mayor and how these elections
мэра этого и как эти выборы
were held about what kind of city? Tell me how many
проходили про какого мра Говори Сколько
people were in Gorlovka in the year? Well, there are people
населения в Горловке ВМ году было Ну нар
in the year  they elected
бы есть в году избрали от Партии
Evgeniy this Klyop from the Party of Regions. Yes, when they
Регионов Евгения этого Клёпа Да в когда
elected in 2008, there were elections, yes. Or
выбрали в дм году же выборы были да Или
in the
в
tenth year, and in the 14th year, how many
десятом так вот а в 14м году сколько
people out of these 300,000 Yes, they elected
человек из этих 300000 Да выбрали вот
this one on the people’s mayor square and how
этого на площади народного мэра и как
these elections took place, who was chosen, they
эти выборы происходили кого выбрали вот
said some  you have people Wait,
сказали какойто у вас народ Подождите
we understood the topic of talking to you who they
понимали тему с вами разговаривать кого
chose I actually think that the mayor was
выбрали Я вообще я считаю что мэр то был
not Wait a second so that we can
не Подождите секундочку чтобы мы дальше
discuss further You must
дискутировать Вы должны
understand the further fate of his sweat I
понимать дальнейшую судьбу его поте
absolutely don’t know I absolutely don’t know
абсолютно не знаю абсолютно не знаю А ну
Well, that’s who you like and who you chose  So I’m
да вот кого вы как и кого вы выбрали Вот
interested, I just knew that
мне интересно я просто я знал вот что
elections were taking place there, there were
выборы происходят там избирательные
candidates there, and so on. Next Yes And how they were
участки кандидаты и так Дальше Да А как
chosen And who This is Well, look, I’m not
выбрали И кого Это Ну вот смотри я же не
complaining about you, you have some kind of your
претензию к вам вот вы у вас какое-то
own vision, I didn’t go there for me  it’s
своё видение у меня я не был там мне
interesting because they say one thing
интересно потому что у нас говорят одно
on TV, you have another, here you are as a
по телевизору у вас другое вот вы как
person who was there, how you
человек который там был как вы его
chose him, how these elections took place
выбрали как эти выборы происходили
How many people chose him Well, you need to
Сколько человек его выбрало Ну надо же
understand the historical context or not
контекст понимать исторический или нет
historically Well, how many
исторически Да ну сколько вот в этом
three hundred are there in this historical one?  Gorlovka
историческом вот трёхсот сная Горловка
Yes, as I understand it, Well, yes, yes, someone chose him somewhere on a
Да я так понимаю что Ну да да его где-то
square in Gorlovka. These are
на площади в Горловке кто-то выбрал Вот
the people who stood on Well, you
люди которые стояли на Ну вы же
understand the historical context is that
понимаете контекст исторический то что
historically, I don’t argue with the historical
исторически я ж не спорю с историческим
context, just How many people
контекстом просто Сколько человек
Tell me in this historical context
Скажите в этом историческом контексте
so that I
чтобы я
understand
понимал
Well, okay, we had a bunch of
А хорошо ладно у нас была у нас куча
these industries. Yes, I can
этих было производств Да я могу Вам
list for you all the factories, steamships, they
перечислить все фабрики заводы пароходы
had deputies who you
от них были депутаты которые вы ско ещё
once again how many people stood in the
раз ещё раз сколько людей стояло на
square when you were elected people's mayor
площади когда выбрали вас народного мэра
Well, probably 50 thousand probably  50 thousand
Ну тысяч наверное 50 наверное тысяч 50 у
in your city and there was no rally 50,000 but
вас в горх и не было митинга 50.000 но
what are you telling me or I’m telling you
что это вы мне говорите или я вам говорю
Yes, I’m telling you there were no
Да это я вам говорю не было 50.000 на
rallies in your throats 50,000 right now come on look come on
митингов в горла вот сейчас давай смотри
so come on
давай так давай
Sri what’s the name of that sucker you
Сри как зовут того лоха которого у вас
elected  there, like at this fifty
избрали там типа на этом пятидесяти
rally, well,
митинге ну
come on, tell me
давай ну ты скажи
how I’m doing now, no, tell me, you’re
как я вот сейчас не ну ты мне скажи Ты
thinking the same way, well, there were 50,000 of you, but I
же соображаешь тож Вы то ж вас 50.000
didn’t say that
было вот не сказал что проголосовала
50,000 people voted, I see that in
50.000 человек я смотрю вот есть в
Gorlovka, 100 people were elected as acting
Горловке 100 человек избрали исполняющие
people’s mayor  There was
обязанности народного мэра Вот был
Sapunov Sapunov there was no such thing, I don’t
Сапунов Сапунов не было такого был я не
know, it’s May five years, don’t let the people’s
зна вот май пяты год не давай народный
mayor, the people’s mayor, the people’s mayor, like, well, it’s
мэр народный мэр народного мэра типа ещё
important that they sorted them out every month,
ну важ там перебирали их те каждый месяц
some 100 people, yes, like, perei birat of
каких-то 100 человек да типа переи бират
the new mayor, no, then your mayor is like how  his
нового мэра нет то ваш мэр типа как его
name is for the fourteenth year, look, that
зовут за четырнадцатый год смотри то
is, the fourteenth year, I say May of
есть четырнадцатый год я говорю май
the fourteenth year, let's oh, here's
четырнадцатого года Давайте о вот ещё
April, the fourteenth year,
апрель четырнадцатый год
so Alexander
так Александр
Sapunov, here's April, here's the news v.ru site
Сапунов вот апрель чего вот новости v.ru
Russian site, here's April 14, 1414,
сайт российский сайт вот 14 апреля
right here, just the very
четырнадцатого года прямо вот как раз
first day Yes, they  Alexander
самый первый день Да им стал Александр
Sapunov became the people's mayor at a rally in front of the
Сапунов народного мэра на митинге перед
buildings of the city executive committee of Gorlovka,
зданиями городского исполкома Горловки
self-defense activists elected And so
избрали активисты самообороны И так
on Everything now, I’ll look right now and
дальше Всё вот сейчас я прямо
not What photos
посмотрю так вот не Какие фотографии
50,000 Are you kidding me there are thousands of people there,
50.000 Вы прикалываетесь там тысячи
I said that you were elected,
нету я сказал что избрали ты
you said I asked How many
человек ты сказал я спросил Сколько было
people were there  square that's when they voted For
людей на площади вот когда голосовали За
this mra you said 5050 was yes yes Where are
этого мра ты сказал 5050 было да да Где
50 thousand there is no it’s
50 тысячи нету
you looking at photographs I’m
вообще это ты фотографии смотришь Я
looking at photographs well maybe not those
смотрю фотографии ну а ну может а не те
Well where can I see those I don’t know
А ну а где можно посмотреть те я не знаю
I don’t know them but you don’t know Yes interesting
я их нето а не знаете Да интересно
interesting just like that oh oh well And
интересно просто так о э хорошо А ещё у
we also had a joke like that honey wait That
нас был прикол такой меду подожди То
is, it turns out look it turns out that
есть получается смотрите получается что
you had a legally elected president not a
у вас был законно избранный прези не
president this city mayor Yes there
президент этот городской голова Да его
was no law then you didn’t have a
не было закона тогда ты что не было
law look you no he was elected by all
закона смотрите вы нет он избраны всеми
residents  Gorlovka at the official elections
жителями Горловки на официальных выборах
Yes, this dude Sapunov, no
Да вот этого чувака Сапунова никакие
elections took place, there were no
выборы не происходили не было
votes, ballots arrived And
там голосования приходили бюллетени И
so on. Just some 100 people
так дальше Просто каких-то 100 человек
like you Yes, they came and said This
типа вас Да пришли и сказали Этот
man will now lead from
человек будет теперь руководить от
our gangster formation and Gorlovka And
нашего бандформирования да горловкой А
which gangster formation Well, I don’t know  there
какого бандформирования Ну не знаю там
were about You don’t know or you don’t know
были об Вот ты не знаешь или не знаеш
they were different they were therefore
разные были они же поэтому
gangsters ban formation famine
бандформирования бан формирование голод
you can’t even imagine how it all
ты даже не представляешь как это всё
happened I can imagine look, I told
происходило Я представляю вот смотри я
you they
тебе говор
put them in the
посадили на
basement
подвал
Ukra Zako from Koto they elected Zhite
Укра зако из кото избрали жите
Donbass go flour they took them and put them in the basement
Донбас го мука взяли посадили на подвал
So he’s not
так он не
Gorlovsky, he was elected in Gorlovka.
Горловский он избранный в Горловке был
Come on, for God’s sake, you were elected to Gorlovka,
Да ладно ради Бога избраны Горловке
wait,
подожди ты
now you teach the context of general history that
Сейчас контекст обще истории учишь что
what happened is not you, now it turns out that
происходи не вы сейчас получается
you admit that you
признаёте в том что вы
and this Russian
какие-то с российским вот этим
Bel took a blow about the Maidan, why about the
Белем взяли подили про Майдан зачем про
Maidan with the Maidan? Everything  it’s clear to
Майдан майданом Всё ясно
the president Show that in May what’s wrong with the
президенте Покажи что на май что с
Maidan and for example what’s
майданом и например что с майданом не
wrong with the Maidan no one was elected on the Maidan there was no one
так на Майдане никого не избрали не было
on the Maidan we’ll vote he will be the
что на Майдане проголосуем будет
president he wasn’t not you
президентом тот не было не ты
wait
подожди
May on the Maidan no one expelled the
Май на Майдане никто не изгонял
president to ask
президента к задал
Kora there
Коре
was a legally elected president
был законно избранный президент
Yes, the story is the story, the legally elected
Да расказ рассказ законно избранные
deputies were taken away, the mayors were, and they were, and
депутаты забраны мэры были да и были и
everyone remained. The
все Остались Верховная Рада сри
Verkhovna Rada, the Verkhovna Rada, no one. New again, once
верховную Раду никто Ново ещё раз ещё
again, no one of the new deputy. So I’m telling you,
раз никто нового депутата Так я тебе
no one on the street said this one
говорю никто на улице не сказал вот этот
will be a deputy, no one was there. Nobody
будет депутатом ни одного не было Никто
from the street.  appointed President
с улицы не назначил президента
Turchynov was a deputy of the Supreme Council
турчинов был депутатом Верховного Совета
elected by the citizens of
избранный гражданами
Ukraine No, he was not from the street, he was VM in the
Украины Нет не с улицы он был ВМ году на
elections Yes, he was elected as a deputy, look,
выборах Да был избран депутатом посмотри
he was not appointed elder of
не его назначили старшим
Ukraine in the elections, he was a
Украины на выборах он был в 14 году был
deputy of the Supreme Council in 14, no one elected him from
депутатом Верховного Совета его никто с
the street, he was already  2 years since the
улицы не избирал он был уже 2 года с
year, you
года депутатом Верховного
can’t pick someone up from the street as a Supreme Deputy, you
нельзя с улицы взять изде человека
can’t, and in Ukraine, wait, I’ll tell you a story.
нельзя и в Украине подожди я тебе расска
Look, in Ukraine, no one has done this
Смотри и в Украине никто так не делал
anymore. Yes, they haven’t done it seriously at all in
больше того Да вообще не делали серьёзно
Ukraine, and in the opposite direction, this law
Украине а в обратную сторону этот закон
works again, look in Ukraine,
работает ещё раз смотри в Украине
yes  Turchinov was appointed Chairman of the
да турчинова назначили председателем
Supreme Council of the Verkhovna Rada because the
Верховного Совета Верховной Рады потому
Verkhovna Rada appoints from among its
что Верховная Рада назначает из своего
members Yes, the head of the Verkhovna
состава Да руководителя голову Верховной
Rada, absolutely everything that surprises you here, they
Рады абсолютно всё что тебя ещё тут
didn’t bring
удивляет не привели какого-то не привели
someone from the street, like me, and they
человека с улицы например меня да и
said he will be deputies, he will be
сказали он будет депутатами он будет
the head of the Supreme Council  they didn’t bring
главой Верховного Совета не привели
anyone, they put no one in the basement, no
никого не посадили на подвал никакого
head of the Supreme Council, and instead
голову Верховного Совета да и вместо
they took someone from the street, and here you have
него кого-то с улицы взяли вот а у вас
Russian militants. Yes, they captured, they
российские боевики Да захватили
captured the city of Slavyansk, the city of Gorlov,
захватили город Славянск город Горлов
where the legally elected mayors were thrown into the
куда законно избранных мэров Кинули на
basement, and then they say everyone who was
подвал А по потом говорят всех кто был
against it  this gang
против этого этого бандформирования
was thrown into the basements of everyone How many
кидали на подвалы всех Сколько в
people passed through the basement in Gorlovka You
Горловке людей прошло Через подвал уж ты
were already there, tell me how many you
там был расскажи Давай сколько ты даже
can’t even imagine what it was, how many
не представляешь что это было сколько
people passed through the basement in Gorlovka,
людей прошло в Горловке через подвал вот
you are a witness of it all Well, tell me No, let
ты свидетель этого всего Ну расскажи Нет
’s go back to this how many people
давай мы вернёмся к это сколько людей в
Gorlovka I already scratched your face
Горловке Я тебе уже расчесал морда тебя
for the Maidan in your [ __ ] Yes, now
за Майдан пово в говне твоём Да теперь
your Gorlovki are back
вернулись твои Горловки
dazi uto people in Gorlovka were Gorlov do
дази уто людей в Горловке было Горлов не
n’t let’s go back to how many heads were killed in
давай вернёмся к сколько убито головн в
Gorlovka how many militants were killed Gorlov
Горловке сколько боевиками убито Горлов
in Gorlovka by Ukrainian militants killed
в Горловке украинскими боевиками убито
at
на
15 let’s start everything came to Gorlovka  some
15 начнём всё пришли в Горловку какие-то
militants Yes, you yourself admitted to the city mayor of Klyop,
боевики Да городского главу Клёпа вы
you yourself admitted that he was
сами признали вы сами признали что его
taken to the basement And they tortured him there, wait, be
забрали на подвал И пытали там подожди
silent Well, why did you
помолчи Ну что ты по депутата рыбака ВС
flog his stomach and throw him into the river?
пороли ему живот и кинули его в реку
they were thrown
сотрудничать с этими боевиками бросали
into the basement by militants Tell me how many people in Gorlovka
на подвал Скажите сколько в Горловке
were in the basement, not a single breach Well, there
людей были на подвале ни одного бреши Ну
was a sting in
вот клёп был на
the basement Look, we read we read So let’s read
подвале Вот смотри читаем читаем Так
with you, it’s already been
давайте почитаем вместе с вами это жеже
known for a long time read Well, where was he, they
давно известно читать Ну где он был пом
let him go, so it’s known, he
отпустили так известно
told me Yes, too,
с рассказывал Да тоже
what’s his name?  they took money to the basement of Kak Vyga, how did you get it to
как его брали на подвал Как выга деньги
these militants of yours? Yes,
как выку вот этим боевикам вашим Да
his relatives paid a ransom so that they
платили выкуп родственники его чтобы его
would let him go from the basement, it was like this
отпустили из подвала было же такое было
and now you will shyly open your eyes,
и вы сейчас стеснительно отворите глазки
yes Well, how come you don’t know, the whole of Gorlovka
да Ну как это не знаете вся вся Горловка
knows, and the bearded Budulai doesn’t know, but
знает а бородатый Будулай не знает но
that’s how  -that’s not the truth, you know,
это как-то не это правда знаете потому
because because everyone knows because in the
что потому что все знают потому что в м
year when all this was where did MR disappear,
году когда это всё было куда МР пропал
MR is sitting in the basement, the whole city is buzzing,
МР на подвале сидит весь город гудит да
like they installed a new mayor in his place, yes
типа нового мэра вместо него поставили
Everyone knows and everyone knew everyone knew
да Все знают и все знали все знали а
how many people were raped in Gorlovka  these
сколько изнасилованных горловк вот этими
bezler vtsa there were how many Yes Look Yes
безлер вца было сколько Да Посмотрите Да
in the prosecutor's office how many statements there are yes
в прокуратуре сколько заявлений есть да
How many people to run away how many
Сколько людей убежать сколько
people how many people ran away fled from
людей сколько людей убежало убежало из
Gorlovka How many from these type of
Горловки Сколько от этих типа боевиков
Russian militants Yes because you are in
российских Да потому что вы вот есть в
Ale Ang Dori Let's speak out
Але Анге Дори Давай выговори
ladies
дами
va Ukraine will liberate you
ва Украина прит освободит будете в
to live in Rostov and the people in Gorlovka
Ростове свом жить а люди в Горловке
will live normally. Glory to Ukraine,
будут жить нормально Слава Украине вон
come on, let’s just roll out how ashamed they are to
Давай вот так мы раскатали как им стыдно
admit. Yes, with you
признавать Да при ты
G yours, with the
Г ваше
mayor elected by all the thousands of the city and the agglomeration. They were thrown into the basement,
агломерацией мэра Кинули на подвал
mocked and shot down, there were tortures, there were so
издевались и сбивали там пытки были
many of these
сколько этих э
evidences already  there is what
уже свидетельств есть что там
happened there people say Yes Who
происходило люди рассказывают Да Кто
went through all this yes the mayor directly he
прошёл через это всё да мэр прямо он
wrote as a journalist after his release Yes
журналистом писал после освобождения Да
and how he was pushed there Yes and how his
и как его туда затолкали Да и как
relatives paid the ransom everything is known
родственники выкуп платили всё известно
everything And these nits they understand everything and
всё И эти гниды они ж всё понимают и
begin Well, the historical context must be
начинают Ну исторический контекст надо
understood historical  the context must be
понимать исторический контекст надо
understood, and once again on the Maidan, no one
понимать да ещё раз на Майдане никто не
elected a president from the street, no one
избирал президента с улицы никто не
elected any deputies from the street, the
избирал никаких депутатов с улицы
Supreme Council, as it was, the Verkhovna Rada
Верховный Совет как был Верховная Рада
remained, and no one took it and
так и осталась Да никто не взял и не
said, this guy from the street will
сказал вот этот ээ чувак с улицы будет
now be a deputy was not completely
теперь депутатом не было было полностью
legitimate government Yes, completely if
легитимная власть Да полностью если у
they have Yes, some 10 militants came Yes with
них Да пришли какие-то 10 боевиков Да с
weapons Yes and they say Everything now you dude
оружием Да и говорят Всё теперь ты чувак
will go to the basement whoever squeaks no, also to the
пойдёшь на подвал кто писк нет тоже на
basement and this one will
подвал а этот будет от нашего имени
measure the measure on our behalf Yes this is
мерить мерию да вот это и есть
Russian terrorism in Ukraine  Yes,
российский терроризм в Украине да
despite the revolutionary events,
несмотря на революционные события
Ukraine retained the legitimacy of the government, the
Украина сохранила легитимность власти
legitimate
абсолютно действовала легитимный
Supreme Council, the Verkhovna Rada, the parliament,
Верховный Совет Верховная Рада парламент
all the deputies were those who were
все депутаты были те которые были
elected, so the Supreme Council can
избраны так Верховный Совет может
appoint the head of the Verkhovna Rada from among its members,
назначать из своего состава голову у
so it’s all there,
Верховной Рады так это всё есть так
so these Bastards, yes they
поэтому эти [__] да они знают они
know they know that  The end of theirs is near because,
знают что конец ихний близок потому что
uh, Kherson was returned and everyone sees that
ээ Херсон вернули да и все видят что
Russia cannot pass a
Россия не может под какой-то блин
year and a half before the offensive under some damn Avdeevka
авдеевкой полтора года до наступления
And in the girl, this is near Donetsk itself, they
пройти А в девка это под самим Донецком
see that they give Ukraine Storm Shadow,
видят что Украине дают там Шторм Шедоу
they give these attacks sy And so on
дают вот эти атакам сы И так дальше
Ukraine  is growing stronger and stronger, they will
Украина стаёт всё сильнее и сильнее
give you another F16, and these Gorlovskys will
дадут ещё F16 да и эти горловские будут
generally squeak like mice. Glory to Ukraine,
вообще пищать как мышки Слава Украине
support the Armed Forces of Ukraine
поддерживайте Вооружённые силы Украины
because we must do everything so that
потому что мы должны сделать всё чтобы
these Bastards who, uh, mocked
вот эти [__] которые ээ издевались
our citizens and even our
над нашими гражданами Да и над нашей
country, at best, run away somewhere-  then
страной в лучшем случае убежали куда-то
to the heroes Slava subscribe to my
в рашку героям Слава подпишись на мий
Telegram right now the axis of wine and
Telegram прям зараз ось вин а
popk is even more and more important YouTube is
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
driving us through the skarg ODS into your ban
загоняет нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан
and I don’t show a lot of videos to people
и дуже багато вдео не показую людям
at the moment I don’t show information about streams
вчасно не показуе информация про стрими
For this purpose, we need Mali operational
Тому для того щоб ми Мали оперативний
sound  'language to write directly at once and while there in
зв'язок пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegra okm video sche tezh tsikava and
телегра окм видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and we will blame you
корисна информация и мы повинни вами
trim postiyny operational link
трима постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno VD togo chi show you about it
незалежно ВД того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
write
пиши